[

{ "question" : "topic0_q000","type": "text", "path" : "", "cA" : 2, "iA" : false, "ans" : [ "topic0_ans000_1", "topic0_ans000_2", "topic0_ans000_3", "topic0_ans000_4" ] },
{ "question" : "topic0_q001","type": "image", "path" : "barcelona", "cA" : 0, "iA" : false, "ans" : [ "topic0_ans001_1", "topic0_ans001_2", "topic0_ans001_3", "topic0_ans001_4" ] },
{ "question" : "topic0_q002","type": "image", "path" : "trevi", "cA" : 1, "iA" : false, "ans" : [ "topic0_ans002_1", "topic0_ans002_2", "topic0_ans002_3", "topic0_ans002_4" ] },
{ "question" : "topic0_q003","type": "text", "path" : "", "cA" : 3, "iA" : true, "ans" : [ "topic0_ans003_1", "topic0_ans003_2", "topic0_ans003_3", "topic0_ans003_4" ] },
{ "question" : "topic0_q004","type": "text", "path" : "", "cA" : 0, "iA" : false, "ans" : [ "topic0_ans004_1", "topic0_ans004_2", "topic0_ans004_3", "topic0_ans004_4" ] },
{ "question" : "topic0_q005","type": "image", "path" : "celinedion", "cA" : 3, "iA" : false, "ans" : [ "topic0_ans005_1", "topic0_ans005_2", "topic0_ans005_3", "topic0_ans005_4" ] },
{ "question" : "topic0_q006","type": "image", "path" : "london", "cA" : 1, "iA" : false, "ans" : [ "topic0_ans006_1", "topic0_ans006_2", "topic0_ans006_3", "topic0_ans006_4" ] },
{ "question" : "topic0_q007","type": "text", "path" : "", "cA" : 0, "iA" : true, "ans" : [ "topic0_ans007_1", "topic0_ans007_2", "topic0_ans007_3", "topic0_ans007_4" ] },
{ "question" : "topic0_q008","type": "audio", "path" : "", "cA" : 1, "iA" : false, "ans" : [ "topic0_ans008_1", "topic0_ans008_2", "topic0_ans008_3", "topic0_ans008_4" ] },
{ "question" : "topic0_q009","type": "audio", "path" : "freddiemercury", "cA" : 0, "iA" : false, "ans" : [ "topic0_ans009_1", "topic0_ans009_2", "topic0_ans009_3", "topic0_ans009_4" ] },
{ "question" : "topic0_q010","type": "audio", "path" : "", "cA" : 2, "iA" : true, "ans" : [ "topic0_ans010_1", "topic0_ans010_2", "topic0_ans010_3", "topic0_ans010_4" ] },
{ "question" : "topic0_q011","type": "audio", "path" : "", "cA" : 1, "iA" : true, "ans" : [ "topic0_ans011_1", "topic0_ans011_2", "topic0_ans011_3", "topic0_ans011_4" ] },
{ "question" : "topic0_q012","type": "audio", "path" : "", "cA" : 3, "iA" : false, "ans" : [ "topic0_ans012_1", "topic0_ans012_2", "topic0_ans012_3", "topic0_ans012_4" ] },
{ "question" : "topic0_q013","type": "audio", "path" : "", "cA" : 2, "iA" : false, "ans" : [ "topic0_ans013_1", "topic0_ans013_2", "topic0_ans013_3", "topic0_ans013_4" ] },
{ "question" : "topic0_q014","type": "audio", "path" : "", "cA" : 3, "iA" : true, "ans" : [ "topic0_ans014_1", "topic0_ans014_2", "topic0_ans014_3", "topic0_ans014_4" ] },
{ "question" : "topic0_q014","type": "video", "path" : "calico", "cA" : 3, "iA" : true, "ans" : [ "topic0_ans014_1", "topic0_ans014_2", "topic0_ans014_3", "topic0_ans014_4" ] },
{ "question" : "topic0_q014","type": "video", "path" : "calico", "cA" : 3, "iA" : true, "ans" : [ "topic0_ans014_1", "topic0_ans014_2", "topic0_ans014_3", "topic0_ans014_4" ] },
{ "question" : "topic0_q014","type": "audio", "path" : "calico", "cA" : 3, "iA" : true, "ans" : [ "topic0_ans014_1", "topic0_ans014_2", "topic0_ans014_3", "topic0_ans014_4" ] }

]
